We're going to work on a arm drill that will help you have graceful hand movements in front of you.
I call it painting the wall.
So this one what you're going to start with, let's take one hand first; it's going to, the wrist is going to come down and the wrist is going to come up.
So basically your wrist is going to be leading the movement, and let the fingers follow nice and relaxed where the wrist is going.
Don't let the fingers take over, let the wrist do all the guiding.
Let's make sure that are feet are parallel and are knees are soft.
Our belly buttons pulled in pressing in towards our spine and our chest is lifted, and our arms are relaxed; are shoulders are nice and relaxed.
So let's start with the one hand going up and down.
We're going to keep this right in front of us; you don't want to have it in front of your face so you block yourself.
You want it right in front of your solar plexus.
So we're going to go up and down; let's switch hands, down and up; down and up.
And just let those fingers relax.
Now together you're going to go opposite.
Do it very mechanically at first and then slowly soften it out as you feel comfortable.
It's real easy to actually get your fingers to lead, so try not to let them do that.
Let the wrist do all the leading.